UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
The Witch of Yeouido is coming.
You have been promoted to team manager
at the Financial Supervisory Service,
and confirmed probe into the slush fund
of Hanmin Investment & Securities.
The prosecution
and Financial Supervisory Service
have already formed a task force team.
HANMIN'S DECADE-LONG ALLEGATIONS
"Yehppee"?
Yehppee and I
are getting the ledger together
for whistleblowing purposes.
You can pick up the slush fund ledger
at the president's office
on the 12th floor in Hanmin's head office.
You could end up receiving
a prison sentence.
Yes. I'm prepared for as much.
- Is it not there?
- This can't be.
Maybe someone at Hanmin
found out about you and President Kang?
This is undoubtedly a warning.
Keum-bo!
Go undercover as some entry-level minion?
They wouldn't imagine you doing this
in their wildest dreams.
All right, sorry.
I mean, you're 35.
Who would ever think
you're in your twenties?
I'll proceed
with the Hanmin undercover investigation.
I'll find Yehppee within three months
and retrieve the slush fund ledger.
Let's hurry up.
The president is waiting for us.
It's not like he's waiting out
in the hot sun.
The three Yehppee candidates are
So Gyeong-dong,
Bang Jin-mok, and Cha Jung-il.
His assistant will have to know
who Yehppee is.
Befriend that assistant
and just get the intel you need.
Then focus on finding Yehppee.
What's with the loitering?
Please welcome President Shin Jung-woo.
Hello.
I'm Shin Jung-woo.
Ms. Hong, you've been appointed
as President Shin's new assistant.
Who says the new president
will have a new assistant?
Who would you say the late President Kang
was closest to at the company?
If there was a general manager
he was close to, they might help you out.
Come on. Who would help out
an assistant with no boss?
I could come with you.
We're roommates.
How about this?
You swoop in and show President Shin
how capable an assistant you are.
Not a single person here
can answer my question?
These are anticipated Q&As
for the chairman.
Must read!
I hope this works out.
That means I can continue working
- as your assistant, right?
- Yes.
Thanks.
I spent all night racking my brain,
wondering if I should visit Mr. So
with a box of expensive ribs.
You mean Mr. So Gyeong-dong
in the Trading Division?
President Kang's mentor
and a well-respected,
seasoned veteran in Hanmin.
He's got to be Yehppee.
There's something fishy.
How can you trust her?
You mean Go Bok-hee?
Damn it.
Why does he work in the dark?
My poor heart.
Keum-bo.
Hong Keum-bo.
Have we met, mister?
May I ask you what your name is?
What do you want my name for?
You can't have my beeper number.
I have a boyfriend.
Wait, I…
Ta-da.
Hong Keum-bo, Shin Jung-woo.
Here.
That's yours,
and this is mine.
Every time you're struggling
with a hard decision,
I'll be by your side.
And every time you have
an important decision to make,
I'll be waiting with you.
- Keum-bo.
- Yeah?
We should tell our seniors and colleagues
about our relationship, right?
We should keep it a secret.
I'll deny it all.
I'm not sure
I have much faith in your poker face.
I'm confident
that I won't get caught.
Really?
Most definitely.
Hello, sir. It's Shin Jung-woo.
It's been a while.
I was just wondering…
if you knew
what Hong Keum-bo has been up to.
I'm back.
Jang-mi, you look extra tired today.
I ran a bit. It's been a while.
Being young must be so nice.
Now that everyone's home,
how about a late-night snack?
How does rotisserie chicken sound?
It'll be my treat.
Yes!
But it's almost midnight.
We can't order any deliveries.
Oh, right.
The RA made that very clear
at the orientation.
It does sound really tasty though.
Hello, sir.
I'm calling from the women's dorm,
Room 301.
Can we get two rotisserie chickens?
Two bottles of beer too.
Thank you. See you there.
Do you know what sets
humans apart from animals?
It's that we humans use tools.
- Jang-mi.
- Why me?
Do you expect me to do it then?
This is clearly a job for the youngest.
Jang-mi.
Heave-ho.
- Heave-ho.
Stop it.
Heave-ho.
Keep going.
- Cheers.
Eat up.
JEOM'S ROTISSERIE CHICKEN
CREDIBILITY
SUSPICIOUS
This is so good.
Here. Take it.
I'm not a kid.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Hong Jang-mi.
As of today, you're officially recognized
as a resident of Room 301.
"As of today"?
I've lived here for three days already.
Come on, I let you have the pink one.
Thanks.
Who is she to recognize me or whatever?
What's your deal?
Don't dig through my stuff!
Wait, I'm not…
- No, hold on.
- Let go, you thief!
What? Thief?
- Bok-hee.
- Are you okay?
Hey!
You thief!
Who's that at this hour?
Bok-hee.
If she were looking to steal,
she would've gone for your wallet,
not your notebook.
Maybe she already did.
You two, search her pockets.
Go on and search them. Search away.
It's your RA. Open the door.
Put it away.
I heard you shout earlier, Ms. Go.
Are you experiencing issues
with your roommates again?
You are one demerit point away
from eviction.
We're all great friends here.
Maybe the TV was too loud?
We were watching a comedy show.
Right.
We're really into this series, you see.
It's past midnight.
In fact, it's color bars time.
This is the only way.
Bok-hee's bag fell over,
so I was just trying to be nice
and pick up what fell out of it.
That's when she came in
and treated me like some thief.
No, I didn't.
I've always been an honest,
tax-paying citizen.
Taxes? You haven't even received
your first paycheck yet.
Ms. Kim, she's lying through her teeth.
She's a bad seed!
That's enough.
Ms. Go, bring me your bag.
Pardon?
Do you see anything missing?
No.
Any missing money?
It is all there, but…
What about this?
It's a notebook from work,
but I use it as my diary.
With no financial loss
or missing property,
it'd be difficult to call this theft.
It seems there's been
a little misunderstanding.
Let's just settle this amicably.
EPISODE 3: RIGHT UNDER THE NOSE
AND IN THE LINE OF FIRE
Chuseok, the nation's biggest holiday,
is fast approaching.
With a four-day holiday this year,
train stations and bus terminals
across the country
are bustling with people heading home
to spend time with their families.
Let's find out more
about the holiday traffic.
The nation's 20 million people
are once again on the move for Chuseok.
The highways have come
to resemble massive parking lots
with the gridlocks caused
by the influx of homebound traffic.
The lengthy delays for the past two days
had travelers face six-hour travel time…
JANG-MI'S SMILE (REPEAT)
"Jang-mi"?
Screw that.
Daejeon saw its highways
at a virtual standstill
with the convergence of holiday traffic…
Gather around, Room 301.
Happy Chuseok!
We should celebrate the holiday too.
Living under the same roof
and sharing meals makes us family.
This is so good.
Try that too.
Look at this big chunk.
Seriously?
Did you really show up empty-handed
to a table set by your seniors
and expect to feast?
But you didn't cook anything, either.
The braised short ribs
are really good, Mi-sook.
Hey, turn that computer off.
I can't sleep because of you!
Are you sure it's not
the guilt keeping you awake?
Did you already forget
that I helped you keep your job?
Hey!
One of us will end up moving out.
And for your information,
I'm not moving out.
I could say just the same.
Oh my gosh.
I guess she got kicked out.
Do you want to sleep in our room?
I didn't get kicked out.
I'm fine.
Please make me rich.
I want to get married.
Please let me find Yehppee quickly
so I can return home.
I beg you.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
WISHING ALL OF THE HANMIN FAMILY
A BOUNTIFUL CHUSEOK
HANMIN REWARDS WITH FULLY RIPENED RETURNS!
Come on now.
Why not? Spicier is better.
Ms. Hong, is the cafe open today?
It's so bitter.
Never heard of two, two, two,
the golden ratio?
Half your job is making coffee.
You really should go back to Admin
and relearn the basics.
Come here for a second.
You know Ms. Go in Admin?
The spinster who's almost 30.
There's a new president in town,
so how do you think
she managed to survive?
Life must be so easy for women.
But don't honey traps
and brute force feel a bit outdated?
Times have changed. Right?
General Manager Cha Jung-il.
What? Are you curious too?
You are, aren't you?
Shut that mouth of yours.
Times have changed.
What?
You should stop spreading nasty rumors
and act your age now.
Hey!
Did you hear about Ms. Hong
from Risk Management?
I heard Cha from Research
has it out for her.
Yeah.
But I heard he was the one who started it,
talking about how the new president
is keeping Go Bok-hee around
because she set a honey trap.
Yeah, and after he did,
Ms. Hong told him to shut up.
Still, assigning her that translation task
meant for foreign-trained staff
is taking it too far.
There's no way a high school grad
could finish that by tomorrow morning.
I know, right?
I heard Cha has it out for you again.
Yes, well…
I'm sure you'll do obnoxiously well, but…
You can speak a bit of English, can't you?
Just a bit.
I think it'll be faster if I do it myself.
Jeez.
Why wait? I told you to go on ahead.
GLOBAL STOCK MARKET REPORT,
TRANSLATED COPY
You couldn't help anyway.
I cheered you on in my heart.
Let's go.
Wait.
LAXATIVE
NORA'S LAXATIVES
CHA'S VITAMINS
Don't you think that's a bit childish?
Revenge is meant to be petty.
That's the way to piss them off.
Jang-mi.
You're not going to join in?
Well…
RECEIPTS FOR EXPENSE REPORTS
Are you constipated?
Good morning.
- Hello, sir.
- Let's have another good day.
Hello, sir.
GLOBAL STOCK MARKET REPORT,
TRANSLATED COPY
To the future. To the world.
Hanmin.
MULTIVITAMINS
This is my first team meeting
since I was hired.
It's our first one as well.
This is Risk Management's
first-ever meeting.
But still, I see you managed
to prepare all this.
That wasn't me.
It was me.
Come on, it's the female employee's job
to put out the drinks
and snacks for the meeting.
Noted.
I need to get this over with
and find Yehppee.
Now, we'll start the meeting
on Hanmin's information-sharing
system development.
Let us begin.
We're not alone in pursuing
an internal information-sharing system.
Since last year, many companies
have begun implementing such systems.
These internal workspaces
for communication and collaboration
are collectively referred to as
the intranet system.
The Risk Management Division?
They can't get anything done.
They have no brainpower
or manpower.
We need to outsource.
They…
First, we must develop a system
that can be easily used by all,
even without a manual.
If you look at the second factor,
- we need a system based on rank…
- Are they actually working?
I will do my best to build
an information-sharing system
that faithfully implements
all the elements I've discussed today.
Thank you.
But the most important part,
the development timeline, is missing.
No need to rush it. We'll just…
Three days.
Come on now. Is that even possible?
Possibility isn't a factor. We must do it.
It's a directive from the president.
And Mr. Lee is very talented.
Ms. Hong, you don't know
what you're talking about.
Even industry professionals
couldn't complete it in three days.
I will make it happen!
Good luck! You got this!
I knew it.
Let's go!
Great. Good luck.
INFORMATION-SHARING SYSTEM
DEVELOPMENT DAY 1
You're so much faster than I expected.
Thanks.
But you made a coding error.
Here.
Sorry. That was a typing error.
Mr. Lee.
You're doing great.
She's a pro
at the carrot-and-stick approach.
I can't tell who's the manager
and who's the new hire anymore.
Ms. Hong, do you even know
what you're talking about?
This is the moment
I use my secret weapon.
Oh my.
My hair is just so in the way.
I missed it.
It's so far back.
You're going to rewind it that much?
INFORMATION-SHARING SYSTEM
DEVELOPMENT DAY 2
Lunch time.
How about spicy pork stir-fry?
Mr. Lee, let's resume after…
Did you not go home last night?
Could your hair be any greasier?
No. This is my 29th hour in the office.
Mr. Lee, you need to eat.
Let's go get some lunch.
I have Mr. Lee's lunch right here.
She's going to bring him
a chamber pot at this rate.
Do you need one?
I'm okay for now.
Eat up.
Let's go, Big Al.
- What should we eat?
- Spicy pork stir-fry!
INFORMATION-SHARING SYSTEM
DEVELOPMENT DAY 3
MISS BEER
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
It's done!
Is it all done?
Team dinner time.
We did it!
No, we didn't do it.
Manager Lee Yong-gi did it.
You gave us
the most excellent performance.
Well done.
I'm so proud of you!
Thank you.
It was only possible
because of you, Ms. Hong.
Thank you.
INTRANET PROJECT COMPLETION REPORT
PRESIDENT SHIN JUNG-WOO
You finished sooner than I expected.
I'm sure you're already aware,
but I didn't build it.
Ms. Hong Jang-mi and Manager Lee Yong-gi
gave it everything they had
to make it into a reality.
Hong Jang-mi and Lee Yong-gi…
It's a leader's job to enable employees
to stay focused on their work.
Chairman Kang asked me
to provide you with guidance
to ensure that you develop
into a leader befitting Hanmin.
Me?
Why?
So you'll basically be taking on
the role of Mr. So.
He started tutoring my uncle
on the stock market
when my uncle was a college student.
After my uncle joined the company,
he served as…
a loyal aide.
A "loyal aide"?
Yes.
But you know
that our chairman
also has a daughter, right?
Feel free to play both sides.
INTRANET SYSTEM ANNOUNCEMENT
ALL INTERNAL MATERIALS WILL BE SHARED
VIA THE "INTRANET."
INTRANET SYSTEM
PLEASE LOG IN TO ACCESS
They're only making life difficult
with this nonsense.
This would only be a challenge
for the general managers.
Youngsters learn fast.
I'm young.
I'm in my prime.
The intranet makes it so much easier.
We're making
half the copies and deliveries.
I know, right?
I heard they worked three nights straight.
Seriously?
Didn't you say you'd eat your hat
if Jang-mi got it done?
When did I say that?
And it's not like
Hong Jang-mi did it herself.
The intranet.
That's right. Albert, my son, made it.
It makes life easier. It's nice.
- Good morning, sir.
That's not like you at all.
We were hearing feedback
on the new intranet system.
Everyone gave five stars.
They are all very satisfied with it.
Is that so?
President Shin, what are your thoughts?
It has an intuitive design
that maximizes usability.
Division Manager Oh
graciously credited his team.
Really?
Our Albert is
just so humble, isn't he, sir?
I told him to take it easy,
but he does his name proud.
"Noble and bright."
He nobly thinks about
the company's bright future.
All right, everyone.
Our job is done for the year.
Don't do any work until next year.
That's all!
Yeah! No more work!
PERSONAL DETAILS
GO BOK-HEE
Maybe I should try Go Bok-hee again.
No, let's move on to
So Gyeong-dong straight away.
PERSONAL DETAILS
SO GYEONG-DONG
NOTES: DOG LOVER
Maybe Yehppee is the name of his dog?
Let's see…
Oh my, I'm so honored.
Mr. Lee.
Do you happen to know
the name of Mr. So's dog?
So pretty…
I mean, Yehppee.
Yehppee?
Are you sure it's Yehppee?
Of course. I heard about it
while drinking with So-Bang-Cha.
"So-Bang-Cha"?
Why don't you
Know
How I feel about you?
They all differ in age,
year of hire, and rank, but they're close.
That's why they got that nickname.
You could even call them
the living witnesses
to every rise and fall of Hanmin.
I heard the late president
really trusted
all three members of So-Bang-Cha.
That's right. It seemed like that.
Who did he trust the most?
Jeong Won-gwan.
I mean, Mr. So.
I see.
Hello, sir.
- Hello there.
- He's our new hire.
So Gyeong-dong.
The legendary trader of Yeouido.
In the securities market,
where returns are a measure of character,
he's admired not only for his talent
but also for his integrity.
He's a Hanmin man to the core,
turning down any and every job offer
that came his way all these years.
- They hired a lot this year.
- Yeah.
What would you like?
- Kimchi pork stir-fry for me.
- Kimchi pork stir-fry?
Yes, understood.
Hello, this is from Mr. Cha.
Thank you.
- Hurry.
- A copy?
Yes, hurry.
And Ms. Kang, bring more coffee.
- Yes, sir.
- Get me a refill.
Sorry.
My apologies.
Get it together.
- What would you like?
- I already told you the second one.
Quickly.
Oh no.
Please don't fall.
Darn it.
Thank you so much.
We should help each other out, Eun-joo.
It's just so hard.
Since I'm the youngest,
I have to grab lunch
for all 20 traders by myself.
They yell at me
for getting their orders wrong,
for being so slow,
and for delivery mistakes.
But you know what's even more annoying?
Even after stomaching all that criticism,
I'm still hungry for food.
Eat up, Eun-joo.
It's so tasty.
By the way, how is Mr. So Gyeong-dong?
My boss?
He doesn't eat lunch.
Apparently, he's been like that
for 20 years.
Nine to six.
He only ever leaves his desk
to go to the bathroom.
But still, he never yells at me.
Starting tomorrow, how about I help you
since my team isn't busy at all?
Let me wipe that for you.
RISK MANAGEMENT DIVISION
Good morning.
What's that?
Is it a gift?
- For Ms. Hong?
- Yes.
To thank her for her guidance and support.
I bought some handmade cookies
that would go perfectly with coffee.
What about for us?
Neither of you contributed anything.
I also know
how to nitpick and micromanage,
but I held back.
Hold on.
What's with the sudden perm
and highlights?
Highlights?
You got highlights?
I'm going to need to have
a conversation with Ms. Hong.
- About what?
- Why?
About how office romances ruin lives.
- That's not what this is.
- It clearly is.
- That's a misunderstanding.
- I don't think so.
No, you can't… Darn it.
Hold on. Where's Ms. Hong anyway?
Did she call out?
You're not supposed to touch this.
Damn it.
What would you like for lunch?
Would you like Kimchi pork stir-fry again?
Yeah, let's go with that.
Now, shall we get started
on another exciting day?
Let's once again survive today.
Let's survive as long as we can.
Beyond the Han River.
- To the World! To the Future!
- Hanmin!
- Hanmin.
Would you like to place your lunch order?
Just the usual for me.
Sure.
HANYE ELECTRONICS 11:27
YEHPPEE?
Big Al, let's grab
pork bone soup for lunch.
That sounds great,
- but I have plans.
- With who?
With the chairman, my dad,
and Mr. So from Trading.
Really?
Ms. Hong, join us for lunch.
I have to help Trading
with the lunch deliveries.
Enjoy your lunch.
You'll look even more haggard
if you skip meals.
Let's go eat lunch.
I'll see you later.
I jumped through hoops to get them
from a key shop down in Cheonggyecheon.
They can open pretty much
all locked drawers and filing cabinets.
These are the master keys.
TEN MINUTES TO THE MORNING SESSION CLOSE
- Enjoy your lunch.
- Thanks.
Ms. Kang, no cucumbers in mine, right?
- You said anything, so…
- Are there cucumbers?
Are you kidding me?
GENERAL MANAGER SO GYEONG-DONG
Dump all your Hanye Electronics shares
at the limit down.
Once you sweep the order book,
we'll step in and clean it up.
Just make sure
we get a clean start at 11:27.
HANYE ELECTRONICS
PRICE: 9,050 WON
GENERAL MANAGER SO GYEONG-DONG
Hey.
Where's my lunch?
Jang-mi.
What are you doing?
I need coffee.
Coming.
I'll be right back.
CASH SELL
CONFIRM SALE
HANYE ELECTRONICS 11:27
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
What's wrong with you?
Damn it.
CONFIRM SALE
You crazy bastard.
How much are you dumping at limit down?
CORRECT/CANCEL
Is this Korea Exchange?
Please cancel the 11:27 order
for Hanye Electronics from Hanmin.
Ms. Hong from Risk Management?
There's no way she was smart enough
to prevent an order-entry blunder.
She's just a new hire,
a minion,
a high-school grad.
What does she know?
So who's the trader
behind the three-billion-won screw-up?
Who knows?
That idiot can forget about
ever working in Yeouido again.
But that Ms. Hong…
I feel like I've seen her
somewhere before.
The interview, remember?
She's the cheeky one who raised her hand
because we didn't ask her anything.
She was the one who pointed out
the exam question error?
That little one
likes to nitpick as if it were a hobby.
I'm actually worried about Mr. So.
This is complete nonsense!
He claims he made the order-entry error
due to a keyboard malfunction.
It didn't seem intentional…
Unbelievable.
Are you trying to cover
for your subordinate right now?
I guess one more slip
and the whole company will go under.
We're discussing executed trades
with the relevant brokerages.
But still, the error was detected,
and the order was canceled immediately.
We requested the Korea Exchange
to cancel the order,
which helped prevent additional losses.
I heard some lowly female employee
was the one who canceled it.
Who cares about that right now?
I was just worried about her going around,
spreading her "heroic" tale
and damaging the company's image.
I'm just concerned, that's all.
More importantly,
I've received a tip
that this incident has the FSS considering
an investigation into us.
What? Goddamnit!
Is it true that a female employee
from Trading canceled the order?
No.
It's the new hire in Risk Management.
Do you mean Ms. Hong Jang-mi?
- Hey, you!
- Jeez.
Thanks to you,
I've had the worst indigestion recently.
Listen, blending in is barely enough
to get you by right now.
How can you go and attract
even more attention?
Who cares if Hanmin makes an order error
and loses three billion won?
That's none of your business.
Look, my hand reacted
before I could think.
You're so painfully predictable.
I have to carry around antacids
because of you.
Wait, how did you find out?
Who told you?
"Three billion won"?
That's quite detailed.
If only no one else knew.
Word has spread from Yeouido
all the way to Euljiro.
Was it on the news?
The news? As if.
The Yeouido Pirates.
The Yeouido Pirates? What's that?
YEOUIDO PIRATES
MAIN MENU, COMMUNITY, ETC.
HANMIN ORDER ERROR INCIDENT
ANOTHER HISTORIC INCIDENT IN THE
SILENT BATTLEFIELD OF THE STOCK MARKET!
Breaking news.
A 20-year-old high school graduate
employee saved Hanmin?
"A 20-year-old high school graduate…"
It can't be, can it?
Around 11:30 today,
Hanmin's Trading Division
witnessed an order-entry error
of the century.
It was an error that could've cost
the company three billion won.
The kicker in this story is
the unexpected heroine who saved the day.
Hong Jang…
PRICE: LOWEST
BUY, SELL
SELL
The heroine sensed danger in the air
and threw herself
to rectify the situation.
She was neither a high-paid trader
nor a foreign-trained analyst,
but a lowly entry-level employee
with a high school diploma.
Her name was Hong Jang-mi.
BREAKING NEWS: 20-YEAR-OLD FEMALE
HIGH SCHOOL GRAD EMPLOYEE SAVED HANMIN!
The Yeouido stock market
is where you make your living.
How can you not know
about the Yeouido Pirates?
From stock-market rumors
and backroom gossip at hostess bars
to top-tier corporate intel.
All those come from the Yeouido Pirates,
the PC Communication site.
The moderator
calls themselves the Captain,
but nobody knows who they are.
Some say they're
a retail investor from Myeongdong,
while others say
they're a retired politician or a hacker.
The rumor mill churns them out.
But you know,
based on the caliber of their intel,
they're clearly
a hotshot in this industry.
The Captain of the Yeouido Pirates?
I've never heard of them.
Wait, how do you know about this
when I just heard about it?
Do you think I got this far
just on my card-playing skills?
You always push your luck
and suffer alone in the end.
I received my invite and joined ages ago.
The Yeouido Pirates, that is.
I still manage to maintain
good relationships with people,
unlike you.
Right.
So I have neither friends nor colleagues.
That's what you're saying, right?
I didn't need this gossip rag
to be good at my job.
Besides, we shouldn't be letting
such baseless rumors dictate our actions.
Still, I guess we should check it out.
Send me an invite.
- I can't.
- Why not?
You get one invite per account.
Then you can just invite me.
I've already sent mine to Nam Dong-gi.
You chose that jerk over me?
Why did it have to be
Nam Dong-gi, of all people?
Damn weasel.
My stomach is upset again.
Jang-mi.
Long day at work?
Mi-sook, have you heard of
the Yeouido Pirates?
Yes. I signed up recently.
Then can you send me an invite?
Recommend me.
Oh, I already used mine
on my branch section chief today.
I see.
I heard that Queen Bee
hasn't used her invite yet.
Let me give you some advice.
…and just bring her that.
WOMEN'S MAGAZINE
PARK JIN-HUI
MINJU BANK
The scale of this slush fund is…
I guess that's the head office for you.
This job might be too big
for me to handle alone.
I'm back.
What's that in your hand? Cake?
That looks so tasty.
Bok-hee, you like cake too, don't you?
It's too late for cake.
I started my diet yesterday.
Do you know
how many calories are in a cake?
Bok-hee.
Is there any chance you'd invite me
to the Yeouido Pirates?
I already used up my invite.
Let me get this straight.
You all did it for one another
and just left me out?
Enjoy the cake.
Oh no. I already used mine up.
What about you, Mr. Bang?
I invited him.
Big Al, let's go to lunch.
To Auntie's?
Let's go to Auntie's, Mr. Lee.
- Shall we?
- Yeah, let's go eat their soup.
That sounds great.
Time for lunch.
Why didn't you ask me?
- Pardon?
- For an invite to the Yeouido Pirates.
I can do that for you.
Really?
- Do you mean it?
- Yes.
Go on then.
Sure.
To start, what's your
PC Communication username?
My PC Communication username?
Do you not have one?
Okay then.
Give me your resident registration number.
Six…
Ms. Hong?
What's the number?
Well…
I'll tell you
after you get back from lunch.
No, I'm fine.
Gosh, I shouldn't have
asked you during lunchtime.
You're going to Auntie's, right?
I'm really fine.
- You must be starving. Go and eat.
- Wait…
I'm not hungry anymore.
Go on.
HONG JANG-MI
780511.
780511…
YEOUIDO PIRATES
REGISTRATION
YOU ARE NOW A YEOUIDO PIRATES MEMBER
DISCUSSION BOARD
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
SEARCHING…
HANMIN BLUNDER
TRADING AT HANMIN SUCKS
- That character dies eventually.
- Hey.
- That's how the character dies.
- He dies like that?
HONG KEUM-BO
SEARCHING…
"HONG KEUM-BO" SEARCH RESULTS
THE FAMOUS HONG KEUM-BO,
I DON'T LIKE THE WITCH OF YEOUIDO
HONG WAS AT MY COMPANY,
ANY SEOUN UNIVERSITY ALUMS HERE?
Look at them all talk trash
behind my back.
Who made this anyway?
MODERATOR: CAPTAIN
"Captain"?
HANMIN ALMOST LOSES BILLIONS OF WON
DUE TO ORDER MISTAKE
What should you do
if the media asks for an interview?
I will not respond to them.
I will let Admin and the PR Division
know about the request immediately.
The Financial Supervisory Service
will be here for an investigation today.
It's just a formality,
but they could speak to you.
So be prepared.
The Financial Supervisory Service?
Who knew we'd be inspecting
Hanmin's internal oversight?
If Hong Keum-bo were around,
she would've insisted on being here.
Just imagine.
- Hey.
- Yes?
We're here to perform our official duties.
Take it seriously, okay?
I was filling out the sell order
when I got thirsty.
When I was looking around for my cup,
a female employee I didn't recognize
suddenly jumped in.
She misunderstood the situation
and caused this mess.
So you're saying
that you made a simple mistake?
I feel wronged.
Why would I ever do anything like that
and throw away my whole career?
Shouldn't we first speak to
Ms. Hong Jang-mi and hear her out?
Shut it.
We believe he made an honest mistake.
It was a devastating mistake
that could've tarnished
the sterling reputation
of Hanmin Investment & Securities.
Excuse me.
Could you get us Ms. Hong Jang-mi--
Someone could be lying.
Just shut up already.
Right? President Shin?
Ms. Go.
Please summon Ms. Hong Jang-mi
from the Risk Management Division.
Yes, sir. I'll see to it immediately.
You've reached Risk Management.
Hong Jang-mi,
the president is asking for you.
You'd better run up here.
Right now?
Why do you look like that?
I'm just a bit nervous.
Where's everyone?
That's why I told you to hurry.
It was a complete mess.
Please summon Ms. Hong Jang-mi
from the Risk Management Division.
Yes, sir. I'll see to it immediately.
ANTACID
Sir?
- What's wrong?
- Are you okay, sir?
Sir?
Sir, are you all right? What's wrong?
- Call for an ambulance now! Hurry!
- Okay.
Sir, are you all right?
What's wrong, sir?
Sir?
That hurts, you punk.
He's hurting! He's in pain!
Sir.
Hold on a second.
Keep hitting him.
Sir! Director Yun!
YEOUIDO HANUI HOSPITAL
If it weren't for my killer acting skills,
your whole operation
would've been belly up.
Hey.
You pay for this today.
You're really okay, right?
There are plenty of fake patients here
who are worse off than me.
Besides, you're in no place
to worry about me.
You just worry about yourself, okay?
Hanmin Investment & Securities
has decided to conclude this by firing
Hong Jang-mi, the entry-level minion
with a high school diploma.
You're their scapegoat.
You'd better prepare for your return.
Why would I be kicked out?
I refuse to leave.
Can you look into the accounts
of Assistant Manager Jung in Trading?
I'm sure he received
a retainer fee beforehand.
We'll carry out
an internal probe of our own.
Our higher-ups
have already been swept off their feet.
What?
One day, we'll be together
Even if we're apart now
My very existence depends on yours
I'm only alive because you exist
The Korean stock market
is only open from nine to three.
So why the hell
does it get busier and nastier
after the sun goes down?
That's Chairman Kang's specialty.
Cash handouts under the table.
Don't tell me you're jealous.
- Yeah.
- What?
No, it's nothing.
His son-in-law is a former official
at the Ministry of Finance and Economy
and my immediate senior
in the civil service.
Jeez.
Money follows connections.
And I have no connections whatsoever.
You don't need to take it that far.
However!
Even today,
I invested in you, Hong Keum-bo!
A long-term investment!
So don't forget that
and keep digging until the end.
I'll extend your leave as much as I can.
Slow down.
That's too hot.
DISCIPLINARY HEARING NOTICE
HONG JANG-MI, RISK MANAGEMENT DIVISION
GROUNDS: HANYE ELECTRONICS ORDER ERROR
What's a disciplinary hearing?
It's putting a bad employee on stage
to punish them for their wrongdoing.
And what exactly did I do wrong?
We're planning to dismiss Ms. Hong,
the one who reported the incident
to the Korea Exchange.
She didn't do anything wrong.
It sounds like she'll be terribly wronged.
Grievances may be resolved
through proper compensation.
A leader must put the organization
before personal sentiments.
I believe you understand
what I'm trying to say.
President Shin, why don't you give us
your reasoning first?
Yes, sir.
There are three people involved.
A general manager, a trader,
and a staff member.
If someone has to take responsibility,
the entry-level employee
would pose the least risk.
And…
And?
It will also be the easiest.
Good.
Pay attention, Albert.
You need to learn this.
Watch and learn, kid.
I'll continue trying my best
to become a good mentor.
Great. Thank you very much.
Hanmin Investment & Securities
has decided to conclude this by firing
Hong Jang-mi, the entry-level minion
with a high school diploma.
You're their scapegoat.
She didn't even have dinner.
She'll be fine.
She's young and full of life.
What if Jang-mi gets fired?
She'll be fine. She's young.
She's clever.
She'll find another job in no time.
What?
It's already our second team meeting.
Who knew it'd be
for Ms. Hong's disciplinary hearing?
Ms. Hong.
You might be too young
to know about this masterpiece,
but this 1976 American film
helped shape the man I am today.
After a boxing match,
the protagonist, Rocky,
screams out, "Adrian!"
his girlfriend's name.
That's when the audience realizes it.
He, in fact,
was not defeated.
Rocky loses on points.
What I'm trying to say is,
don't talk back in there
like you do with us.
And don't be too disappointed
if it doesn't go your way.
I can always write you
a recommendation letter.
More importantly, the most iconic scene
in Rocky isn't the final one.
Despite having nothing but poverty
and a tattered tank top to his name,
Rocky meets heavyweight champion Apollo
without backing down and declares
that he does not participate
in fixed fights.
I'll be back.
So you want her to get beaten up?
Come on, Mr. Oh.
No, that's not what I meant.
Rocky…
I wasn't sure if I should tell you
what Hong Keum-bo had been up to.
After all that, Keum-bo joined
the Financial Supervisory Service
and was successful enough
to be called the Witch of Yeouido.
That is, before she screwed herself over.
What do you mean by that?
She was trying to go after Hanmin
and their slush fund recently,
but things went awry,
and she was demoted to a regional office.
Jung-woo.
Just let her be.
Don't look for her.
She wouldn't want to see us.
We turned our backs on her, after all.
She was really young then too.
One minute.
Sir, the disciplinary hearing
will start at 9:30.
All right. Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
HANMIN FINANCIAL AUDIT
9 YEARS AGO, 1988
CHEONGSAN ACCOUNTING FIRM, SEOUL
What is it? Are there a lot of issues?
Hanmin made sure
the numbers added up before sending them.
They can't do that.
Inflated financials, cooked books,
and audit report wordplay.
It's all unacceptable.
- Mr. Yun.
- Yes, sir?
You're right, the kid is bright,
but she's also clueless.
CHEONGSAN ACCOUNTING FIRM
CEO KIM NAK-JEONG
CPA SHIN JUNG-WOO
Hanmin Investment & Securities
is a VIP client at our accounting firm.
If we feign just a bit of ignorance,
we all get to reap the benefits.
A lie that benefits all.
No such thing exists.
Hey!
I'll be sure to explain it to her
so she understands, sir.
What an idiot.
Jung-woo, can you step outside?
Sorry, Keum-bo.
I'll persuade him to do the right thing.
Sir…
Don't be a stranger now.
In the Hanmin accounting fraud case…
All right. Let's see this through.
- Please take good care of us.
- Thank you.
Taking care of the country's economy
is no joke.
- Get back safely, sir.
- Sure. Thanks.
CHEONGSAN ACCOUNTING FIRM
Mr. Yun, the accountant
who was being investigated by the police,
committed suicide
by jumping from his apartment building
around 3 p.m. today.
Don't do anything.
Let's do as I say, just this once.
Stay quiet.
Stay quiet about what?
Someone died.
The company will make that right somehow.
- So we just--
- You.
You shouldn't do that.
You can't!
What does clinging to that
so-called conscience get you?
It's not about gains.
It's about not losing it!
And is whatever you gain worth losing me?
HONG JANG-MI
Hello.
I am Hong Jang-mi.
UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
A post on Yeouido Pirates
claims you were fired.
- Is it true?
- Me?
There are rumors
that an insider was involved
in the Hanye Electronics incident.
Oh my g--
I'll expose the truth.
I refuse to leave until I do.
I refuse!
What is all this?
Why do things keep blowing up?
Why? I need to find Yehppee!
I found you, my peacock!
Do you want to hang out?
I despise romance.
Don't tell me you're here to see me.
I'm not here for you, Ms. Hong Jang-mi.
I'm here for Hong Keum-bo.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim